pomodoro-tracker.com 2019-10-25

# The Pomodoro Tracker — A useful tool for time management based on Pomodoro Technique.

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. Please read the privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how Pomodoro-Tracker collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the service. 

When registering on the service, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your details to help you with your experience. 

The Pomodoro-Tracker collect information from you when you register or enter information on the service. 

We may use the information we collect from you when you register or use service features in the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest or other service feature.

We use regular Malware Scanning. 

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. 

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the tasks in your TODO list. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. 

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below. 

[Kirill Klenov <[email protected]>](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#ea828598848f8e99aa8d878b8386c4898587)

Last Edited on 2017-05-13
